Excuse me, sir. Sir. Yeah. Is this your
yacht? Yeah, but what's with the camera right there?
I have a channel with 10 million followers.
I go all over the world interviewing the most
successful people. I'm asking yacht owners what they
did to be able to afford a yacht.
Well, I own a hedge fund. You own a
hedge fund? Correct. For how long? Almost 28 years. Over
these 28 years, what was the most amount of
money you made in a single year? We did about
30 million in sales. I had been a part
of a partnership where we had bought a company
for $25 million and had sold it for $55
million three years later. I would say about $300
million. $300 million? Yeah, more or less.
Question for you. I have 10 million followers.
I have the biggest business. Can I interview
you for one minute? How long have you been
an entrepreneur? A little bit longer than you.
What was the most amount of money that
you made in a single year? Me or the
company? The company? The company I think did, let's
say, would be $8.5 billion, I think, last
year. How about for yourself? I ate every
day. How can somebody own a yacht in today's world?
Miami is one of the richest cities in the
entire world. In fact, it is the number six
city in the United States with the most
millionaires. There's over 12 billionaires that live in
Miami. Today, I flew out here to
come find and ask millionaires and billionaires how
they built their wealth and how you can
become financially free in today's world. With that
being said, let's get this video on the way.
Speaker 1
Speaker 2
Speaker 3
Speaker 4
Speaker 5
Speaker 6
Speaker 7
Speaker 8
Speaker 9
Speaker 10
Speaker 11
Speaker 12
Speaker 13
Speaker 14
Speaker 15
Speaker 16
Speaker 17
breathing
Speaker 16
Speaker 20
Speaker 21
Speaker 12
Speaker 15
Speaker 17
Speaker 18
Speaker 22
Speaker 24
Speaker 27
How many businesses do you own?
Right now?
Yeah.
I have five.
Five businesses?
Yes.
How long have you been a business owner?
Oh my gosh, my first time I was an
equity partner in a company, I was 24 years old.
How old are you now?
I'm 50.
You're 50 years old.
I am.
Did you come from a lot of money?
I came from nothing.
I grew up with four kids, a single
mother on food stamps, living in a trailer behind
my grandparents' home.
What was your turning point to financial freedom?
When you grow up with lack,
you realize what you don't want.
So you're like, how am I going to fix this?
And I just remember thinking at a young age,
at nine years old, I started my first paper
I'm like, I just need to start hustling, start working.
I'll figure it out along the way.
A lot of people don't want to hear that
the come up is a struggle and it's a journey.
But by the time I was 18 and
everybody else was just starting to think about working,
I had been working for a decade.
So I had sales expertise.
I had hustle ingrained in me.
So when I actually started my first job
out of college, I crushed everybody near me because
I had the work ethic and I also had the
experience and expertise that I had built in that come
up.
Were you good at selling?
I mean, I could sell ice cream in Eskimo.
Wow.
So give us a quick sales masterclass right here.
Give me a lesson about sales.
The most important thing about sales to
always put yourself in the other person's shoes.
Too often people think about, here's
what I want you to have.
Here's why I want you to have it.
That's an epic fail.
The right way to do it is to put
myself in your shoes, figure out the problem that you
need solved.
Think about and empathize with how you're
feeling, how you got there and start speaking
that to you.
Immediately you're going to feel a connection with me.
You're going to feel a trust with me.
And you're gonna say, this girl gets my pain point.
Now I can ask her, Hey,
can you solve that for me?
And wouldn't you know?
Yes, I can.
And that's how you really sell people.
You realize they don't use that.
In school, right?
Well, they need to start teaching it.
Did you have to sacrifice a
lot when you were coming up?
Oh my gosh.
Of course.
I remember in my twenties,
all my friends were getting married.
Everybody was having babies.
I didn't take one day
off from work for four years.
Not one vacation, not one day.
All my friends lived in Boston.
I lived in Boston.
I moved to the middle of Michigan in
the middle of nowhere, Saginaw, Michigan, not somewhere
an ideal location.
People want to go.
I was 24 years old.
I gave up everything because I wanted to
put myself on the map in regards to business,
create some credibility and name for myself and some wealth.
And it all worked out.
When you were coming up.
Growing your businesses.
Did you have a lot of people
that were hating on you or doubting you?
Even my own family has, right?
Like people who, it doesn't mean
they have to hate on you.
They might love you and they want to
hold you back because they're scared for you.
It doesn't have to be haters.
I think that that's a confusing
point for a lot of people.
My second book is called Overcoming Your Villains.
It's about getting all negative people out of your life.
That's key to success.
But sometimes the people that are really holding
you back and holding you down are the ones
that love you because they're afraid for you.
You have to be willing to say, I feel you.
I see you.
I thank you.
I'm grateful for you.
And I'm going to still move forward anyway.
So it's safe to say that even though they're
your family or your loved ones, they may not
know what's actually best for you.
No one is going to know
what's best for you other than you.
You've got to tune out that noise.
Maybe they couldn't do it.
That has nothing to do with whether
you're going to be successful or not.
You got amazing advice.
Oh, thank you.
I'm so happy to be here with you.
I appreciate you.
Thank you for your time.
You guys, we're at our next destination right now.
The Miami Beach Yacht Harbor.
Home to some 10, 20, 30 million dollar yachts.
So we're going to be going around, seeing if
we can get into these gates, go up to these
docks where the yachts are parked to see if
we can ask the yacht owners what they did
to become rich out here in Miami.
So let's waste no more time and let's go around
and see if we can find some people and go
see what they have to say.
Come on.
Oh, I'm sorry, bro.
Can we come in?
No, no, no.
Why not?
It's private.
Private?
Yeah, yeah.
Are any of them open?
Yeah, you got to go to the office.
Are the ones?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
As you guys can see, man, since we are
at the Yacht Harbor, the Yacht Marina out here,
it is very hard to get into these
places because these people are very private, very secretive
with how they made their money.
But you know us and we're going to do whatever
we can and whatever it takes to go get the
game for you guys out here in Miami.
So let's go find some and
go see what they have to say.
Come on.
All right, you guys.
So we were able to get
into one of the docks out here.
So we're going to try and find some people
out on these boats and see how they were able
to accumulate their wealth out here.
Sir, question for you.
What is this?
Is this your yacht?
No.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
Yeah.
Is this your yacht?
Yeah, but what's with the camera right there?
I have a channel with 10 million followers.
I go all over the
world interviewing the most successful people.
I'm asking yacht owners what they did
to be able to afford a yacht.
Well, I own a hedge fund.
You own a hedge fund?
Correct.
For how long?
Almost 28 years.
Over these 28 years.
What's the most amount of money
you made in a single year?
I would say about $300 million.
$300 million?
Yeah, more or less.
Actually?
Yeah.
Could I ask you a couple
of questions for the channel real quick?
Sure.
Thank you for having us on board.
Absolutely.
Nice to meet you.
Can we ask you a couple
of questions on how you became successful?
Yeah, sure.
So my first job, I was on Wall Street.
I worked for a company called Nesbitt Burns.
It was actually acquired by Bank of Montreal.
And I then developed a hedge fund, which
I was running about 4,000 traders and about
600 employees.
We did about 3-4% of the U.S. markets in volume.
In 2010, I then basically...
We created a fintech company
and switched from trading to execution.
And did that for about another 7 or 8 years.
And one of the big banks in Canada looked
at us, loved it, and we sold the company.
Have you ever lost money?
A lot of money.
What's the most amount of money
you lost in a single year?
I'll tell you what I lost in one day.
What'd you lose?
A little over $8 million.
$8 million?
What happened?
I was trading a stock that didn't
go my way, and it was pretty bad.
But over time, we learned from our
lessons, made it back, and that's it.
That would cause a lot of people
to crash out and do something crazy.
How did you maintain composure and
not go off the deep end?
What was it that kept you?
What kept you going?
I had a bad day, thought about it,
and I said, it's just a bad day.
And we're going to go
back and do whatever we can.
So I learned from that mistake.
I learned that one thing is
always know what your risk is.
And always don't underestimate anything at all.
Because anything can happen any minute, any time.
We don't have any control over anything over this world.
And I learned that.
So right now, when I decide how much
risk I'm going to take in any business,
I'll make sure that I could afford what I'm
investing if it goes to zero or it fails.
Some of the richest people that I've
ever met that worked on Wall Street,
they never actually placed a trade.
It just got rich off
of like a handshake, closing deals.
How important was networking for you
when you were on Wall Street?
Yeah, that's very interesting.
So I think, first of all, you could trade.
You could do a lot of things yourself.
But the most important thing is networking,
where you want to meet people
that you want to connect with.
And one of the craziest stories
is my partner and I, Brian,
when we had the broker-dealer,
there was one of the biggest companies on Wall Street,
the biggest traders on Wall Street.
The chairman was about to leave.
And we invited him to come to see our company.
And basically, I told Brian, I said,
you got to call him.
You met him at the golf tournament.
You got to call him right now.
This is now.
He's going to remember you.
Bring him over and let's show him what we do.
And he did that.
The gentleman was extremely respectful and super kind.
And he did come to the company.
He looked at us and
he looked at me and said,
how the hell did you build this so undercover?
It's an amazing business.
And he became the chairman of my company.
And from then on, this is where
we got more and more people that were,
you got to be able to
attract the best people in the industry
if you want to make a lot of money.
I love how you said when he had
to call him, he had to call him now.
How important was speed for you?
It was everything.
If he didn't call him that like now.
And I remember he ran around the pool and
he was a little nervous and he called him.
And the guy said yes.
And he came to me and
he said, wow, he's coming over.
But then we had to
have something real that, you know,
that was valuable for him to invest.
And he did invest and became the chairman.
That was like where we pivoted in the company.
And that's where that took us to the next level.
So speed is extremely important.
When you want something, you got to go for it.
And manifesting is the most important
thing you can do in business.
So talk to me about that manifesting though,
because not a lot of business people,
they don't really talk about the mindset.
Too much.
But it seems like that's been very important for you.
It's very important.
I mean, manifesting is something I do every
day and I believe in it so much.
And I've done that since
I was like 10 years old.
Like if I really, really want something,
I'm going to go for it and
I'm all do everything to get it.
It doesn't matter how I'm going
to get it legally, of course,
but everything that I need to do,
I'm going to do to be
able to acquire what I want.
So what does your self-talk look like?
I mean, it's very different for everything.
I think one of the
self-talks is probably like I smile,
I think, and I go, yeah,
I'm going to get this.
And I know exactly how,
and I think in my head,
what are the steps for me to achieving that?
And I create this whole story
and then I go for it.
You got amazing advice, my friend.
Great. Well, thank you very much.
Thank you so much for having us on.
Guys, Miami has been incredible so far,
and I'm headed right now to go
get my next interview for you all.
But I want to talk real quick about
one of the most important pieces of advice
that I've received from
a hundred million dollar entrepreneur.
And this is for all the business owners out there.
You see, most companies die from indigestion and starvation.
And let me break that down.
When a business starts growing fast,
these can get out of control very quickly.
Sales, inventory, accounting,
everything starts to break down if you
don't have the right systems in place.
And that's why so many entrepreneurs turn to Odoo,
a business management software that
brings everything into just one platform.
So instead of juggling five different tools,
Odoo lets you manage sales, accounting,
and inventory all in one place.
For example, as your business grows,
you know, it becomes
significantly harder managing inventory.
And Odoo automates the entire process.
From tracking stock levels to placing
purchase orders at the perfect time.
So you can focus on scaling instead of micromanaging.
And the best part, you only
use the apps that you need.
And you can try any single app for free or get
a 14 day free trial with no credit card information required whatsoever.
So if you're serious about scaling your
business the right way, check out Odoo.
All you have to do is go down
to the link in the description of this video.
Click that link to check it out today for free.
But with that being said,
let's go get this next interview.
Sir, question for you.
I'm not doing that.
I'm about to have to do that thing.
I have 10 million followers.
I have the biggest business chain.
Can I interview you for one minute?
Credibility matters.
Credibility kills all bad attitudes.
Remember that.
My man, what do you do for a living?
I help companies navigate the regulatory
and clinical pathways for their products.
So you're a business owner.
If you take any supplements or
beverages, more than likely it's my client.
Actually?
Yeah.
How long have you been an entrepreneur?
A little bit longer than a year.
Yeah?
You said longer than a year?
A little bit longer than you.
Yeah?
Can we turn this off for one minute real quick?
What was the most amount of
money that you made a single year?
Me or the company?
The company?
The company I think did, let's say,
would be 8.5 billion, I think, last year.
8.5 billion.
Give or take.
How about for yourself?
I ate every day.
Eight out of 10 companies, they
go out of business in today's world.
What's the most common mistake you see business owners make?
CEO's ego.
Your ego is not your amigo.
Yeah, no.
CEOs will fuck up a good company.
Were you good in sales?
No, I'm great in sales.
You're great in sales.
What's your secret to selling?
Because sales cures everything for a lot of companies.
I don't sell anything. I just find out
what the client needs and I hit his goal.
Is there a question that you're constantly asking people?
Yeah.
Like, what are you doing to get to yes?
Same thing you asked me.
You got a minute?
What do you need?
I'll help you get there.
I'm like the fucking genie.
How about negotiating though?
Because you've been at the table with some heavy hitters.
You're going back and forth.
What's your secret to negotiating?
There's a dollar value to everything.
If I can get your product to market faster
than you can, what is that worth to you?
And I ask, I'll figure out what that is, how much
they're going to make on that particular product within a year.
If I can save them three months, let's say they're
going to do $12 million a year on that product launch.
If I can get a product three months
earlier, I'll make them an extra $3 million.
If I'm charging you 300
grand, then why are you bitching?
You're just made to 3 million.
So it's not what it costs, it's what you get.
Yeah, it's the scale of economics.
If you lost everything tomorrow,
could you make it all back?
Done it four times.
So you've lost it before?
Four times.
How are you getting back every single time?
Same way.
Yeah? What?
Well, what's the X factor each time that you've lost?
It doesn't make it, the widgets are relevant.
Policies and procedures are the exact same.
You just got to do what you got to do.
Treat people right.
Do what they're looking for and outwork everybody else.
Thank you so much for your time today.
You got it.
You got amazing advice.
You guys heard what I said.
I stopped him on the motorcycle because
I said I have 10 million followers.
Understand this, credibility matters.
But just like I said, I have 10 million followers.
That guy made $10 billion with his company.
Crazy good interview out here in Miami.
We got to keep this one rolling and
go get another one out here, you guys.
Come on.
I watch your shit all the time.
Just looking at you.
Hey, real quick, real quick.
How did you get rich?
I did get rich.
That's why I watch you.
So what do you do for a living?
Mechanical engineering.
Engineering?
Yeah.
Do you own a firm?
I own a company.
Yeah?
For how long?
For 22 years.
Did you become a millionaire?
No, I did not.
But I'm trying to be.
You're going to be one.
What did you do in revenue this last year?
We did about $30 million in sales.
$30 million in sales.
And how about, what's the profit on that?
Probably like $2 million, $3 million.
$2 million.
Yeah.
So you're putting a lot
of money back into the business.
Yeah.
So you're building right now.
Constantly building.
So what are you doing to scale the company?
Like what's the biggest thing, the
number one X factor that you're in?
We can't scale unless we have employees, good employees.
Because we're in the field service business.
Is it easy to find them or is it-
No, it's really hard.
It's really hard because no one wants to work.
Who's the most important person you've hired so far?
My twin brother.
Your twin brother?
Yeah.
So are you a fan
of going into business with family?
Because some people say don't go
into business with friends and family.
My dad said, which was funny, he
goes, when he trained us, he's like,
I got to train some asshole so
he'll admire me with my own son.
So your dad was a business guy?
Yeah.
He put us in the business.
How old are you now?
You look incredible from 51.
Thanks.
What's the secret to looking so young?
I go to the gym every morning.
Yeah, you work out every day?
Yeah.
You still put up that 225 bench?
No, I'm at 135.
Regardless though, money stays in shape
at the end of the day.
Yeah, you know what?
It's a whole mindset.
If you go to the gym and
you're dedicated and you go there every day,
you're going to go to work every day too.
Have you ever lost money before?
Yeah.
When you're an owner, you go through cycles
all the time of when you're up and down.
No one wants to cut back.
It's always great to buy great cars
and buy Porsches and all that stuff,
but God forbid you have a bad year,
what are you going to get rid of?
It's always harder to go down, you know?
Do you think everybody's built for entrepreneurship?
No, because some people are great employees, but
at the other end, it's a lot of sacrifice.
Your wife, your kids, everyone's got to sacrifice.
You travel, you're not home every night, so
a lot of people aren't built for that.
They'd just rather take a paycheck, which is great,
but at the same time, it's a lot of dedication.
It's good and bad.
It's hard to start a company,
but it's even harder to keep it.
Appreciate you so much, man.
Appreciate it, buddy.
Thank you, brother.
Guys, this video was incredible, but I
need you guys to like and subscribe
for amazing content I've got coming every single
week because I'm going all over the world
to find billionaires and the most successful business
owners to deliver their advice right to you.
And if you are not
a member of my entrepreneur community,
the number one in the world, the School
of Mentors, you need to become a member.
You can join this community today for free by going
down to the link in the description of this video.
The School of Mentors is number
one in the world for a reason,
because you can get mentored directly from the millionaires
and the billionaires that I interview
on this channel every single week.
I can't wait to see you
on the inside of the community.
And with that being said, I'll
see you in the next video.